Finding Aid for the Louis B. Schnauber (Film Music Society) Collection PASC-M.0157
UCLA Library Special Collections
Louis B. Schnauber (Film Music Society) collection
1910-1927
UCLA Library Special Collections
Schnauber, Louis B. (Film Music Society)
PASC-M.0157
37 linear feet (37 cartons)
The collection consists of 2111 complete sets of orchestral parts for silent films, assembled by Louis B. Schnauber between 1910 and 1927 while he worked as Music Director in more than 25 Omaha theaters. The collection is in the midst of being processed. The finding aid will be updated periodically.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942348463606533
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of 2111 complete sets of orchestral parts for silent films, assembled by Louis B. Schnauber, between 1910 and 1927 while he worked as Music Director in more than 25 Omaha theaters.
The collection is arranged alphabetically by composition title.
- Folders 213-300 (Box 3)
- Folders 301-390 (Box 4)
- Folders 391-485 (Box 5)
- Folders 486-585 (Box 6)
- Folders 586-673 (Box 7)
- Folders 674-709 (Box 8)
- Folders 782-811, 813-829, 831-896 (Box 9)
- Folders 897-940 (Box 10)
- Folders 941-973 (Box 11)
- Folders 974-1024 (Box 12)
- Folders 1243-1296 (Box 17)
- Folders 1297-1346 (Box 18)
- Folders 1347-1404 (Box 19)
- Folders 1405-1472 (Box 20)
- Folders 1473-1523 (Box 21)
- Folders 1524-1577 (Box 22)
- Folders 1578-1630 (Box 23)
- Folders 1631-1674 (Box 24)
- Folders 1675-1735 (Box 25)
- Folders 1736-1781 (Box 26)
- Folders 1782-1844 (Box 27)
- Folders 1845-1909 (Box 28)
- Folders 1910-1979 (Box 29)
- Folders 1982-2032 (Box 30)
- Folders 2033-2074 (Box 31)
- 12th St. Rag (Box 3, Folder 236)
- 1812 Overture. Solennelle, 1913; 22 parts (Box 13)
- Adagio Cantabile (Box 7, Folder 586)
- Adagio Espressivo (Box 11, Folder 959)
- Adeste Fideles. O Come All Ye Faithful, 1908; 12 parts (Box 13)
- Aeolus (Box 9, Folder 797)
- Aesop's Fables-Animated Cartoons (Box 4, Folder 383)
- After Sunset (Box 6, Folder 583)
- After the Dance, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 679)
  General note
  Also composed by William Frisch and Otto Motzan
- Aggravation Rag (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Agitated Hurry (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Agitated Mysterioso (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Agitato (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Agnus Dei. Holy Lord, God Almighty, 1902; 12 parts (Box 14)
- Aida Selection, 1914 (Box 12, Folder 988)
  Also composed by Wm. G. Dietrich.
- Aida. March (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Aisha (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Alabama (Box 11, Folder 951)
- Alabama Moon (Box 4, Folder 340)
- Alabama Slide (Box 3, Folder 230)
- Algiers (Box 1, Folder 83)
  Also composed by Marks.
- Allah's Holiday (Box 8, Folder 724)
- Allegretto (Box 11, Folder 966)
  Seventh Symphony, Op. 92
- Allegro Moderato, 1914; 11 p. (Box 2, Folder 145)
  Scope and Contents note
  Ensemble parts for various instruments.
- Always In All Ways, 1930; 16 p. (Box 2, Folder 204)
  From the Paramount film "Monte Carlo." Also composed by W. Frank Harling.
- America (Box 11, Folder 953)
- America First (Box 7, Folder 654)
- America United, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 443)
- The American Boy (Box 5, Folder 435)
- The American Boy, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 682)
- American Fantasia (Box 11, Folder 949)
- American Festival Overture, 1910; 42 p. (Box 2, Folder 115)
  Ensemble parts for various instruments
- American Home Songs (Box 9, Folder 913)
- American Legion (Box 9, Folder 793)
- American Life (Box 9, Folder 914)
- American Patrol (Box 11, Folder 948)
- The American Red Cross March, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 683)
- American Volunteers, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 684)
- Among The Roses, 1916; 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 154)
- Amorita (Box 6, Folder 513)
- Amorita, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 896)
- Anchor and Star March, 22 p. (Box 5, Folder 425)
- Andalucia (Box 9, Folder 899)
- Andante Cantabile (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Andante Doloroso (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Andante Doloroso, No. 51, 1917; 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 147)
- Andante Doloroso, No. 70, 1917; 8 p. (Box 2, Folder 160)
- Andante Pathetique, No. 10, 1916; 17 p. (Box 2, Folder 163)
- Andante Pathetique, No. 23, 1916; 9 p. (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Andante Pathetique (For General Use), 1916; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 151)
  Copyright assigned in 1919 to Belwin, New York.
- Ange D'Amour (Box 4, Folder 306)
- Angelus (2nd Movement from 3rd Symphony), 1919; 16 parts (Box 14)
- The Animal Fair (Box 8, Folder 745)
  Also composed by Harry La Forrest and Harley Rosso.
- Apache Dance (Box 7, Folder 609)
- Arabia (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Arabian Nights (Box 8, Folder 722)
  Also composed by Wm. Hewitt.
- Arabianna (Box 8, Folder 716)
- Arcady (Box 7, Folder 601)
- Arizona (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Armenia (Box 9, Folder 845)
  Handwritten parts.
  Hymn
- Armorer's Song (Box 4, Folder 378)
- Army and Navy (Box 7, Folder 661)
- Astarte (Box 6, Folder 581)
- At the End of the Broken Down Trail (Box 3, Folder 216)
- Athalia Overture, 1916; 14 parts (Box 13)
- At Nod (Box 8, Folder 765)
- At the Chicken Chaser's Ball (Box 8, Folder 727)
- The Attorney-General (Box 7, Folder 663)
- Auld Lang Syne, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 1158)
  Scope and Contents
  Parts.
- Ave Maria, 1907; 19 parts (Box 14)
- Aviation Tournament, 12 p. (Box 5, Folder 426)
- Aviation Rag (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Awake My Soul. O Salutaris Hostia, 1901; 12 parts (Box 14)
- The Awakening, 1924; 18 pages (Box 2, Folder 146)
  Ensemble parts for various instruments. From "Sam Fox Cinema Impressions Vol. 1."
- Azora. Prelude to Act II, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 1235)
  On item: Orch. Miscellany, no. 125.
  Parts
- Baboon Bounce, 1912; 12 pages (Box 2, Folder 190)
- Baby Peggy, 1923; 14 pages (Box 2, Folder 142)
- Baby Peggy, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 864)
- A Bag of Rags (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Ballet Sentimental (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Ballet and Chorus from G. Rossini's "William Tell", 1906 (Box 12, Folder 1020)
- Barcarole, No. 65, 1917; 10 pages (Box 2, Folder 152)
- The Barber of Seville (Box 35, Folder 8)
- The Bartered Bride (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Battle of the Kings (Box 7, Folder 656)
- Bayadere (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Beau Brummel (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Beautiful Valley of Eden (Box 4, Folder 363)
  Gospel Hymn Series No. 4.
- Becasue of You (Box 8, Folder 695)
- Before the Mast, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 825)
- The Bells of Bagdad (Box 8, Folder 718)
- Berceuse (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Beyond the Moon (Box 3, Folder 251)
  Lyrics by Johnny Gruelle and Johnny Mercer.
- Big Chief Battle-Axe (Box 1, Folder 37)
- The Bird Man (Box 9, Folder 796)
- A Bit of Syncopation, 1921; 13 pages (Box 2, Folder 196)
- Bizzaria (Box 6, Folder 501)
- Blame it on the Blues (Box 3, Folder 228)
- Blood Lillies (Box 6, Folder 559)
- Blue Hawaii (Box 3, Folder 213)
  Also composed by Ira Schuster and Irving Caesar.
- Blue Jeans (Box 3, Folder 227)
- The Bluebird (Box 7, Folder 638)
- The Blushing Rose, 1911; 12 pages (Box 2, Folder 119)
  Ensemble parts.
- Blue Pacific Moonlight (Box 3, Folder 254)
  Also composed by Wallace Herbert.
- Bohemia, 1919; 12 pages (Box 5, Folder 416)
  Also composed by Weslyn.
- La Boheme (Box 33, Folder 7)
- La Boheme. Fantasia, 1903; 25 parts (Box 15)
- The Bombardment, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 838)
- Bonnie Scotland, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 1156)
  Overture. Parts.
- The Boys From Home (Box 7, Folder 666)
- Brass Fanfare (Box 9, Folder 868)
- Bridal Procession (Box 12, Folder 979)
- Bridal Roses (Box 7, Folder 628)
- Brightly Gleams Our Banner (Box 4, Folder 363)
- The Bridal Rose Overture, 1885; 18 parts (Box 13)
- Buena Vista, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 887)
- Buenos Ayres, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 451)
- Buffalo Gals (Box 9, Folder 858)
  Inside cover is tinted film announcement.
- Bullets and Bayonets (Box 4, Folder 310)
- A Bull in a China Shop (Box 7, Folder 587)
- Burlesque on Chopin's "Funeral March", 1927; 18 pages (Box 5, Folder 403)
  From Belwin's "Cinema Burlesques."
- Burning Sands (Box 1, Folder 85)
  Scored by D. Onivas.
- Burlesque on Bizet's "Toreador Song", 20 pages (Box 5, Folder 411)
- Burlesque on Famous Hebrew Melodies, 22 pages (Box 5, Folder 404)
- Burlesque on "How Dry I Am", 1927; 20 p. (Box 5, Folder 405)
  From Belwin's Cinema Burlesques.
- Burlesque on "Home Sweet Home", 1927; 21 p. (Box 5, Folder 408)
  From Belwin's "Cinema Burlesques".
- Burlesque on Verdi's "Miserere", 18 p. (Box 5, Folder 409)
- Butterfly Dance, 1919; 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 144)
- By My Side (Box 4, Folder 351)
  Also composed by Chauncey Gray.
- By the Japanese Sea (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Bye Baby Bunting (Box 9, Folder 863)
- By Wireless (Box 8, Folder 770)
- Cabaret Capers (Box 9, Folder 854)
- Cabin in the Hills (Box 3, Folder 217)
- The Calif of Bagdad. Overture, 1912; 16 parts (Box 13)
- Canary Cottage, 1916; 12 parts (Box 13)
- Cannibal Dance (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Can't We Talk It Over (Box 6, Folder 530)
- Canton Aero Club, 1911; 12 p. (Box 5, Folder 428)
- Canzonetta (Box 7, Folder 594)
- Carissima (Box 9, Folder 894)
- Carmen. Second Suite (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Carnival Queen (Box 7, Folder 614)
- Hungarian Rhapsody No.6. The Carnival in Pesth, 1919; 14 parts (Box 14)
- Castles in Spain, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 450)
- "Cavalleria Rusticana". Prelude And Siciliana. Intermezzo Sinfonico, 1891; 12 parts (Box 13)
- Celebrated Minuet (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Chanson du coeur brise (Box 8, Folder 704)
- Le Chant des Bergers, 1920; 19 parts (Box 13)
- Chacone (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Chansonette (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Chapel Chimes (Box 4, Folder 366)
- Charleston (Box 3, Folder 222)
  Also composed by Jimmy Johnson
- Cheer Up Father, Cheer Up Mother (Box 6, Folder 506)
- Cheerful Litle Earful (Box 4, Folder 345)
- Cherie (Box 3, Folder 280)
  Words by Leo Wood
- Cheritza (Box 3, Folder 288)
  Also composed by Ford and Bibo.
- Cheritza (Box 7, Folder 673)
- Chicken Reel (Box 8, Folder 731)
- Child In Distress-Intense Suffering, 1924; 16 p. (Box 5, Folder 391)
  Selections by Chas. J. Roberts. From Carl Fischer "Film Themes."
- Child's Dream, 1919; 18 p. (Box 2, Folder 149)
  From the "Motion Picture Screen Series" by Gaston Borch.
- The Chimes of Liberty, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 433)
- Chiffonette (Box 7, Folder 590)
- Child of the Arcade. Overture, 1893; 18 parts (Box 13)
- Childish Pranks-Planning Mischief (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Children's Games, 1907; 15 p. (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Children's Party-Animated Cartoons (Box 4, Folder 381)
- The Chimes of Notre Dame (Box 4, Folder 367)
- Chin - Chin (Box 7, Folder 615)
- China Girl (Box 6, Folder 544)
  Also composed by Don Warner and Louis Singer.
- Chinese or Japanese Drama. Prelude (Box 6, Folder 561)
- Chinese Patrol (Box 6, Folder 546)
- Chinatown My Chinatown (Box 6, Folder 558)
- Chinchilita (Box 6, Folder 521)
  Duplicate copy.
- Chinchilita (Box 6, Folder 522)
- Chu-Chu-San (Box 6, Folder 552)
- Cigarette (Box 6, Folder 518)
- La Cinquantaine. Pizzicato Bluette, 1916; 15 parts (Box 13)
- Ciribiribin (Box 3, Folder 282)
- Citizen's Pride (Box 9, Folder 801)
- Civilization (Box 9, Folder 792)
- Cloud Kisser, 1912; 11 p. (Box 2, Folder 175)
- A Cloister Episode, 1923; 17 parts (Box 14)
- Cloister-Chimes (Box 4, Folder 372)
- The Co-Ed (Box 7, Folder 622)
  Also composed by Saul Bernie.
- Collection of Gospel Hymns, 1901; 21 parts (Box 13)
- Columbia the Gem of the Ocean (Box 9, Folder 870)
- Collegiate (Box 7, Folder 621)
  Also composed by Nat Bonx.
- Columbia (Box 7, Folder 657)
- Come Back To-Night in My Dreams (Box 3, Folder 215)
- Comedy Allegro, 1918; 21 p. (Box 2, Folder 156)
- Comic Hurry (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Comical-Frolicking Children, 1924; 13 pages (Box 5, Folder 398)
- Comrades of the Legion (Box 4, Folder 318)
- Contentment (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Le Coq d'Or. Selections, 1920; 21 parts (Box 15, Folder 1138)
- Coral Sea (Box 6, Folder 556)
  Also composed by Herb Brown.
- Cosette (Box 3, Folder 272)
- Country Gardens, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 1146)
  Galaxy no. 269. No. 22 in the British Folk Music Settings series.
- Cradle-Song (Box 9, Folder 835)
- Cradle Rock
  Also composed by Phil Kornheiser.
- Crinoline (Box 7, Folder 597)
- The Crusaders (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Crying Myself to Sleep (Box 4, Folder 350)
- Csikos Et Bohemienne Op.372 No.3. Csardas, 1919; 14 parts (Box 14)
- Cuban Moon, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 463)
  Also composed by Joe McKiernan.
- Cut Yourself a Piece of Cake (Box 8, Folder 739)
- Cyrano. Prelude, Act II, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 1237)
  On item: Orch. Miscellany, no. 43
- Daddy Long Legs, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 675)
- Daigah's Dream (Brazilian Intermezzo), 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 174)
- La Dame Blanche overture, 1913; 14 parts (Box 13)
- Dance of the Cammorists (Box 11, Folder 960)
- Dance of the Hours (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Dance of the Moon Birds (Box 7, Folder 593)
- The Dance of the Goblins, 1902; 12 parts (Box 14)
- The Nut Cracker Suite. Danse des Mirlitons (Box 35, Folder 3)
- The Nut Cracker Suite. Danse Chinoise (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Danse Bacchanale (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Danse Russe Trepak (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Darktown Dancin' School (Box 6, Folder 514)
- The Daughter of Heaven (Box 9, Folder 818)
- The Daughter of the Regiment, 1913 (Box 12, Folder 985)
- Dawn, 19 p. (Box 2, Folder 159)
- Dear Little Boy of Mine (Box 4, Folder 332)
- Dear old Pal of Mine (Box 4, Folder 360)
- Dearie, Won't You Change Your Mind? (Box 3, Folder 265)
- Deep in My Heart, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 866)
- Deep River (Box 10, Folder 909)
- The Deep Purple (Box 9, Folder 799)
- Defender (Box 4, Folder 328)
- Delilah (Box 8, Folder 776)
  Also composed by Fred Fisher.
- Democracy, 1918; 26 p. (Box 5, Folder 412)
- Democracy Forever, 22 p. (Box 5, Folder 423)
  Also composed by J. Bodewalt Lampe.
- Derby Days (Box 8, Folder 764)
- Desolation Over the Steppe, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 1198)
  On item: Galaxy, no. 285
  Orchestral parts.
- Devils March (Box 9, Folder 806)
- Die schone Galathea, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 1022)
- Die Werber (Box 9, Folder 782)
- Dixie Kisses, 1911; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 177)
- Djer-Kiss (Box 7, Folder 646)
- Dodola (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Dolores Waltz (Box 4, Folder 305)
- Don Giovanni (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Don't Mind the Rain (Box 9, Folder 829)
  Also composed by Chester Cohn
- Don't Tell the Folks You Saw Me (Box 6, Folder 573)
  Also composed by Thos. S. Allen.
- The Donkey Trot (Box 7, Folder 607)
- Down By the Old Millstream (Box 8, Folder 751)
- Down By The Winegar Woiks, 1925; 7 p. (Box 2, Folder 143)
  Also composed by Roger Lewis and Walter Donovan.
- Down in a Coal Mine, Op.121, 1896; 12 parts (Box 14)
- Down Old Virginia Way (Box 33, Folder 15)
  Also composed by Gladys Gillette.
- Down South (Box 11, Folder 946)
- Down the Mississippi, 1895; 12 parts (Box 14)
- Dramatic Suspense-Agitated Sorrow, 14 p. (Box 5, Folder 396)
  Selections by Chas J. Roberts. From Carl Fischer "Film Themes."
- The Dragon's Eye (Box 6, Folder 553)
- Dramatic Allegro (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Dramatic Hurry (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Dramatic Intermezzo, 1924; 20 p. (Box 5, Folder 397)
- Dramatic Misterioso (Box 1, Folder 92)
- A Dream, No. 56, 1917; 8 p. (Box 2, Folder 150)
- Dreamy Paradise, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 458)
  Also composed by Erwin R. Schmidt
- Dream a Little Dream of Me (Box 6, Folder 537)
  Also composed by W. Schwandt and F. Andree.
- Dream of Love and You (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dreaming (Traumerei). Scotch Lullaby, 1916; 18 parts (Box 15, Folder 1143)
- Dreams of Erin. Irish Overture, 1902; 12 parts (Box 15, Folder 1142)
- Dreams of India (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Dreams of Love (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Dutch Kiddies (Box 9, Folder 873)
  Handwritten manuscript.
- The Dwarf's Patrol (Box 5, Folder 476)
- Easter Chimes, 1914; 19 parts (Box 13)
- Echoes of Seville, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 889)
- Ecstasi (Ecstasy), 1913 (Box 9, Folder 892)
- Egyptian Impressions (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Einzugsmarsch der Bojaren (Box 12, Folder 979)
- Ekko Fra Norden (Box 11, Folder 971)
- Elsa's Dream (Box 11, Folder 964)
  From Lohengrin
- Emancipation Day (Box 6, Folder 509)
- The Emerald Isle: a Selection of Irish Melodies, 1913; 16 parts, Galaxy, no. 65 (Box 15, Folder 1140)
- Emotional-Pleading-Love (Box 5, Folder 402)
- Emotional-Pleading-Pathetic (Box 4, Folder 386)
- Emotional-Pleading-Pathetic, 1924; 18 p. (Box 5, Folder 417)
- Enchanting Night (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Endearment, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 1166)
  On item: Lib. No. 121
- L'Enfant Prodigue. Madrical and Valse Lente, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 1220)
  On item: Orch. Miscellany no. 14
- [Title Unknown] (Box 11, Folder 958)
- Enticement, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 843)
- Entr'acte et Danse des Bacchantes (Box 11, Folder 958)
- Entrance and Dance of Children, from the incidental music to "The Conqueror", 1906 (Box 12, Folder 1021)
- Entreaty (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Epilogo, 1918; 13 p. (Box 2, Folder 167)
  From "Collection 'Drama,' Scenes Musicales Pour Films Cinematographiques."
- Erl King, 1908 (Box 15, Folder 1179)
- Ernani Grand Selection, 1914; Carl Fischer Inc.; Lake, Mayhew; Verdi, Giuseppi; 19 parts (Box 15, Folder 1135)
- Espana Waltz (Box 9, Folder 893)
- Espanita, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 447)
  Composer's name also listed as G. M. Rosenberg
- Etincelles (Box 8, Folder 767)
- Eugene Onegin. Polonaise (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Evening Song, Moses, Theo.; Schumann, Robert; Carl Fischer Inc. (Box 16, Folder 1207)
- Evensong (Box 7, Folder 592)
- The Evolution of Yankee Doodle (Box 11, Folder 955)
- Expectation Song (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Fabian Romance, 1906; M. Witmark & Sons; Tyers, William H. (Box 15, Folder 1180)
- Fackeltanz, 1889; Carl Fischer Inc.; Meyerbeer, G.; Moses-Tobani, Theo. (Box 15, Folder 1178)
- Fairies-Children's Frolic-Rippling Waters (Box 4, Folder 385)
- Faithful and True (Box 4, Folder 327)
- Falling In Love With You, 1926; 16 p. (Box 2, Folder 134)
- Falling Rose Leaves, 1922; Aborn, Morris; Belwin, Inc.; Sanders, Alma (Box 15, Folder 1181)
- Famous Players Rag (Box 3, Folder 233)
- Fanciful Vision, A, 1918; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Langey, Otto; Rubinstein, A. (Box 16, Folder 1186)
  On item: Galaxy, no. 127.
- Fanfare, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 880)
- Fandango (Box 6, Folder 493)
- The Far Away Bells (Box 8, Folder 693)
- Farewell-Lament-Pathetic (Box 3, Folder 242)
- Fatinitza March (Box 9, Folder 806)
- Faust Selection, 1884 (Box 12, Folder 989)
- Faust. Selections (Box 36, Folder 7)
- La Favorita Selection, 1919; Carl Fischer Inc.; Seredy, Julius S.; Donizetti, Gaetano; 18 parts (Box 15, Folder 1131)
- Fearless and Free (Box 9, Folder 804)
- Feist Sparklets (Box 8, Folder 706)
- Felice, op. 124, 1896; Langey, Otto (Box 15, Folder 1177)
- Fellowship March (Box 4, Folder 337)
- Festival Dance and Valse of the Hours (Box 11, Folder 965)
- Fidelio (Box 35, Folder 10)
- La Fiesta, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 453)
  From "Sam Fox Cinema Impressions"
- Fifth Nocturno, 1903; Carl Fischer Inc.; Leybach, J. (Joseph); Moses-Tobani, Theo. (Box 16, Folder 1199)
- Fifty Million Frenchmen Can't Be Wrong (Box 8, Folder 738)
- Fifth Symphony. Andante (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Figaro's Hochzeit (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Fighting Kid (Box 9, Folder 874)
- Fingal's Cave (Die Fingalshohle) Overture, 1902; 16 parts (Box 13)
- A Finnish Lullaby, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 980)
- Fire Dance, 1927; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Huerter, Charles; Baron, Maurice (Box 15, Folder 1175)
  On item, Galaxy, no. 320
- The Fireflies Picnic, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 439)
- Fiume March (Box 3, Folder 283)
- Five Little Brown Jugs Rag, 1909; 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 172)
- Flags of Freedom (Box 9, Folder 794)
- Flight of the Bumble Bee, 1926; Carl Fischer Inc.; Rimsky Korsakov, N.; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 15, Folder 1174)
- Fluffy Ruffles (Box 6, Folder 503)
- For the Freedom of the World, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 444)
- For You Alone (Box 8, Folder 698)
- For Your Caresses (Box 3, Folder 270)
  Lyrics by Ray Klages and Jack Meskill.
- For Your Country and My Country (Box 6, Folder 497)
- The Forge in the Forest, 1914; 12 parts (Box 14)
- Forgotten Perfumes, 1927; J.W. Jenkins Sons Music Co.; Denni, Gwynne; Denni, Lucien; Wheeler, C.E. (Box 15, Folder 1173)
  Piano score and parts.
  On item: The Theme song featured by Mary Bothwell in John Murray Anderson's Paramount Prologue, "My Lady's Perfumes."
- Forlorn Hopes, 1923; Baron, Maurice; Belwin, Inc.; Delille, Frances (Box 15, Folder 1182)
  Piano conductor score and parts.
- Forosetta, 1902; Carl Fischer Inc.; Roth, Alfred; Arditi, Luigi (Box 16, Folder 1187)
- La Forza Del Destino. Selections, 1902; Carl Fischer Inc.; Moses-Tobani, Theo.; Verdi, Giuseppi; 12 parts (Box 15, Folder 1133)
- Fountain, The, 1924; Miles, Walter E.; Sam Fox Publishing Co.; Zamecnik, J.S. (Box 16, Folder 1185)
  On item: Lib. No. 117
- Four Little Sugar Plums (Box 7, Folder 595)
- Freckles (Box 8, Folder 735)
  Also composed by Milton Ager and Howard Johnson.
- Freischutz (Box 12, Folder 984)
- Frivolette (Entr'acte), 1920; Baron, Maurice; Belwin, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 1184)
- Frivolous Cupids, 1920; Photo Play Music Co.; Schoenfeld, William Charles (Box 15, Folder 1172)
- Frivolous Patrol, 1918; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Goublier, G.; Schmid, Adolf (Box 15, Folder 1183)
  On item: Galaxy, no. 126. Piano conductor score and parts.
- Frolics and Fancies, 1923; Adams, Clifford; Clark, Tom, 1941- --Archives.; G. Schirmer, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 1176)
  On item, Special Series, no. 31
- From the Highlands: a Selection of Scotch Melodies, 1915; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Langey, Otto; 21 parts Galaxy, no. 175 G. (Box 15, Folder 1141)
- From the Northland (Box 11, Folder 970)
- Fu (Box 6, Folder 543)
- Furioso (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Good Gravy Rag, 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 189)
- Galop No. 7 (Box 8, Folder 771)
- Gandramus Igitur, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 865)
- A Garden Dance, 1914 (Box 12, Folder 993)
- Garden of Dreams (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Garden of Love, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 677)
- Gathering of the Braves (Box 36, Folder 9)
- The Gate Ajar For Me (Box 4, Folder 363)
- Gavotte (Iphigenie et Aulide) (Box 9, Folder 852)
- Gavotte Piquante, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 994)
- Gay Gallantry (Box 5, Folder 484)
  From "Hawkes Photo Play Series"
- Gen. Mixup U.S.A. (Box 7, Folder 659)
- General Pershing's Carry On (Box 4, Folder 313)
- The Gentle Dove (A Love Song), 1906 (Box 12, Folder 1002)
- Geraldine (Box 4, Folder 355)
  Also composed by Geo. A. Gibbs.
- Gigolo, 24 p. (Box 5, Folder 415)
- La Gioconda, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 987)
- Gippsland March (Box 7, Folder 658)
- Gitana (Box 6, Folder 512)
- Go Work in My Vineyard (Box 4, Folder 363)
- The Gobbler's Gambol, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 834)
- Goin' to Town (Box 6, Folder 532)
  Also composed by Harold Mooney.
- Golden Morning, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 990)
- Golden Spider (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Gondoliera, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 995)
- Good Fellowship, 1912; 13 p. (Box 5, Folder 421)
- Good Night (Box 3, Folder 226)
  Also composed by Wm. Roettger and Paul Simon.
- Good Scout (Box 6, Folder 499)
- Good-Bye Blues (Box 8, Folder 734)
- Good-bye, Good Luck, God Bless You (Is All That I Can Say) (Box 7, Folder 624)
- Good Bye, 1907 (Box 12, Folder 999)
- Good Night My Child (Box 12, Folder 998)
- Good-Night, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 1011)
- Good Fellowship March, 19 p. (Box 5, Folder 424)
- Gospel Hymn Series (Box 5, Folder 449)
- Gospel Hymn Series (Box 9, Folder 807)
- Gospel Hymn Series, No. 5 (Box 9, Folder 808)
- Gospel Hymn Series, No. 6 (Box 9, Folder 809)
- Gospel Hymn Series, No. 7 (Box 9, Folder 810)
  Various composers.
- Goulash (Box 7, Folder 604)
  Also composed by Jack Egan.
- Grand American Fantasia (Box 11, Folder 954)
- Grandma, Dear Grandma (Box 9, Folder 855)
- Graceful Blondinette, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 1001)
- La Gracieuse (Box 7, Folder 653)
- Grand Aria, The Mad Scene from Lucia di Lammermoor, 1915 (Box 12, Folder 1000)
- Grande Polka de Concert, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 1006)
- Grandioso (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Green River (Box 8, Folder 744)
- Grief-Lament-Pathetic (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Grief-Lament-Pathetic, 1924; 15 p. (Box 5, Folder 399)